Guide to the Winston Weisman Collection of Architectural Photographs [1950]-1973 depicting structures ca. 1850 - 1970 PR 73
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Mounted Copy Prints 1850 -- 1970
  - MANHATTAN, NEW YORK (by street address)
    - 1413 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 123)
      Holland Building
    - 1460 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - 1501 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 125)
      Paramount Building
    - 1515 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 126)
      Hotel Astor
    - 1790 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 127)
      United States Rubber Co. Building
    - 2109 Broadway (Box 7, Folder 128)
      The Ansonia
    - Broome and Centre Street (Box 7, Folder 129)
      Trenckman Building
    - Broome and Crosby Street (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - 429 -- 437 Broome Street (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - 448 -- 452 Broome Street (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - 453 -- 455 Broome Street (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - 461 -- 468 Broome Street (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - 469 -- 475 Broome Street (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - 477 -- 479 Broome Street (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - 484 -- 499 Broome Street (Box 8, Folder 137-142)
    - 484 -- 499 Broome Street (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 143-144)
    - 500 Broome Street (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - 307 -- 311 Canal Street (Box 9, Folder 146)
      Arnold, Constable & Co. Building
    - 329 -- 331 Canal Street (Box 9, Folder 147)
    - 359 Canal Street (Box 9, Folder 148)
    - 361 Canal Street (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - 35 -- 103 Cedar Street (Box 9, Folder 150)
      includes Fisk and Robison, Home Insurance Co., New York Clearing House
    - Central Park West and 72nd Street (Box 9, Folder 151)
      Hotel Majestic
    - Central Park West and 73rd to 74th Street (Box 9, Folder 152)
      The Langham
    - Centre and Duane Street (Box 9, Folder 153)
      Bogardus cast iron factory
    - Centre and Leonard Street (Box 9, Folder 154)
      building for Edwin C. Burt and Co.
    - 163 -- 165 Centre Street (Box 9, Folder 155)
      McCullough Shot and Lead Co. shot tower
    - Chambers Street (Box 9, Folder 156)
      Hudson River RR Passenger Station
    - Chambers Street and College Place (now West Broadway) (Box 9, Folder 157)
      Gerken Building
    - 39 -- 107 Chambers Street (Box 9, Folder 158)
      American News Building, Cary Building
    - Church Street (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Church Street, Dey to Cortlandt Street (Box 9, Folder 160)
      Havemeyer Building
    - 30 -- 99 Church Street (Box 9, Folder 161)
      Hudson Terminal Buildings, Dun & Bradstreet Building
    - City Hall Park (Box 9, Folder 162)
      City Hall
    - 82 -- 90 Cliff Street and 325 -- 337 Pearl Street (Franklin Square) (Box 10, Folder 163)
      Harper Brothers Building
    - College Place (Box 10, Folder 164)
      Stevens' House
    - 16 -- 20 Cortlandt Street (Box 10, Folder 165)
      Metro Telephone Co. Building
    - Duane Street (Box 10, Folder 166)
    - Duane and Hudson Street (Box 10, Folder 167)
    - 160 -162 Duane Street (Box 10, Folder 168)
    - Exchange Place, Hanover and Beaver Street (Box 10, Folder 169)
      Post Building
    - 43 -- 49 Exchange Place (Box 10, Folder 170)
    - 30 -- 38 Ferry Street (no longer exists) (Box 10, Folder 171)
      Chas. A. Schieren & Co.
    - Front Street (Box 10, Folder 172)
      Banks Building
    - Front and Pine Street (Box 10, Folder 173)
      Downing Building
    - Fulton Street (Box 10, Folder 174)
      includes ruins of Phelp's and Peck's Store
    - Fulton and Nassau Street (Box 10, Folder 175)
    - 81 Fulton Street (Box 10, Folder 176)
      Market and Fulton National Bank
    - 139 Fulton Street (Box 10, Folder 177)
      Bennett (Herald) Building
    - 51 -- 55 Franklin Street (Box 10, Folder 178)
      Eagle Building
    - Gold Street (Box 10, Folder 179)
      includes Healy Building
    - Goerck Street (no longer exists) (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Grand and Centre Street (Box 10, Folder 181)
      New Centre Market
    - 55 Grand Street (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - 60 Grand Street (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - 68 - 70 Grand Street (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - 72 Grand Street (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - 74 Grand Street (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - 83 -- 88 Grand Street (Box 11, Folder 187)
    - 89 -- 105 Grand Street (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - 107 -- 113 Grand Street (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - 118 -- 140 Grand Street (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - 255 -- 261 Grand Street (Box 11, Folder 191)
    - Great Jones and Lafayette Streets (Box 11, Folder 192)
      Schermerhorn warehouse
    - 7 -- 13 Greene Street (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - 15 -- 32 Greene Street (Box 11, Folder 194-195)
    - 33 -- 51 Greene Street (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - 57 -- 86 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 197-198)
    - 87 -- 89 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 199)
    - 90 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 200)
    - 93 -- 100 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 201)
    - 102 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 202)
    - 103 -- 105 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 203)
    - 108 -- 112 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 204)
    - 113 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 205)
    - 114 - 123 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 206)
    - 124 -- 128 Greene Street (Box 12, Folder 207)
      includes U.S. Post Office
    - 129 -- 144 Greene Street (Box 13, Folder 208-209)
    - 146 -- 150 Greene Street (Box 13, Folder 210)
    - 666 Greenwich Street (Box 13, Folder 211)
      The Archives (Appraiser's warehouse)
    - 27 Howard Street (Box 13, Folder 212)
    - Herald Square (Box 13, Folder 213)
      Herald Building
    - 37 -- 39 Howard Street (Box 13, Folder 214)
    - Hudson Street -- no address (Box 13, Folder 215)
    - Hudson and Duane Street (Box 13, Folder 216)
    - Hudson and Jay Street (Box 13, Folder 217)
      American Express Co. Building
    - Hudson, Leroy and Morton Street (Box 13, Folder 218)
      Mirror Candy Factory
    - Hudson and Spring Street (Box 13, Folder 219)
      Bradley and Currier Building
    - 1 -- 90 Hudson Street (Box 13, Folder 220)
      includes Irving National Bank
    - 105 Hudson Street (Box 13, Folder 221)
      Pierce Building
    - Irving Place and East 16th Street (Box 13, Folder 222)
      Borgfelt Building
    - Jacob Street (no longer exists) (Box 13, Folder 223)
      leather warehouse for G. B. Horton
    - 284 -- 290 Lafayette Street (Box 13, Folder 224)
    - 295 -- 309 Lafayette Street (Box 14, Folder 225)
      Puck Building
    - 444 Lafayette Street (Box 14, Folder 226)
      Potter Printing Offices
    - 74 -- 76 Laight Street (Box 14, Folder 227)
      Fairchild Brothers and Foster Building
    - Leonard and West Broadway (Box 14, Folder 228)
    - 45 Leonard Street (Box 14, Folder 229)
      includes Rothschild Building
    - 66 -- 76 Leonard Street (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - 85 Leonard Street (Box 14, Folder 231)
    - 405 Lexington Avenue (Box 14, Folder 232)
      Chrysler Building
    - 575 Lexington Avenue (Box 14, Folder 233)
    - 740 Lexington Avenue (Box 14, Folder 234)
      Bloomingdale's
    - 1 Liberty Plaza (Box 14, Folder 235)
      U.S. Steel Building
    - Liberty Street (Box 14, Folder 236)
      Brooklyn Life Insurance Co. Building
    - Liberty and William Street (Box 14, Folder 237)
      Dudley Building
    - 53 -- 67 Liberty Street (Box 14, Folder 238)
      view of stores
    - Madison Avenue and 42nd Street (Box 14, Folder 239)
      Hotel Manhattan
    - Madison Avenue and 52nd Street (Box 14, Folder 240)
      The Berkshire
    - Madison Avenue and 59th Street (Box 14, Folder 241)
      Hoffman Arms Apartment Building
    - 1 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 242)
      Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. Building
    - 51 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 243)
      New York Life Insurance Co. Building
    - 89 -- 95 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 244)
      Emmet Building
    - 380 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 245)
      California-Texas Oil Co. Building
    - 488 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 246)
      Look Building
    - 575 Madison Avenue (Box 14, Folder 247)
    - 37 --39 Maiden Lane (Box 14, Folder 248)
      Lorsch Building
    - 46 Maiden Lane (Box 14, Folder 249)
      Lawyer's Title Insurance & Trust Building
    - Mercer Street between Broome and Grand (Box 14, Folder 250)
    - 15 -- 17 Mercer Street (Box 14, Folder 251)
    - 55 Mercer Street (Box 14, Folder 252)
    - 57 Mercer Street (Box 14, Folder 253)
    - 69 Mercer Street (Box 14, Folder 254)
    - 71 Mercer Street (Box 14, Folder 255)
    - 79 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 256)
    - 91 -- 93 Mercer Street (Box 256, Folder 257)
    - 117 -- 119 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 258)
    - 120 -- 124 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 259)
    - 155 -- 157 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 260)
    - 169 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 261)
    - 171 Mercer Street (Box 15, Folder 262)
    - Mott Street, between Houston and Prince Streets (Box 15, Folder 263)
      F.A. Ferris and Co. Packing Establishment
    - 48 -- 50 Murray Street (Box 15, Folder 264)
      includes Charles Ahrenfeldt & Son Building
    - 75 Murray Street (Box 15, Folder 265)
    - Nassau and Beekman Streets (Box 15, Folder 266)
      Clinton Hall, Vanderbilt Building
    - Nassau and Liberty Streets (Box 15, Folder 267)
      Syndicate Building
    - Nassau and Pine Streets (Box 15, Folder 268)
      Western National Bank
    - Nassau, north view from Wall Street (Box 15, Folder 269)
      Continental Bank
    - Nassau to William, Liberty to Cedar Streets (Box 15, Folder 270)
      Mutual Life Insurance Co. of New York Building
    - 22 -- 26 Nassau Street (Box 15, Folder 271)
      Turner Building
    - 38 Nassau Street (Box 15, Folder 272)
      Morton Trust Co.
    - 139 Nassau Street (Box 15, Folder 273)
      Nassau Bank
    - 148 Nassau Street (Box 15, Folder 274)
      United States Hotel
    - 150 Nassau Street (Box 15, Folder 275)
      American Tract Society Building
    - Park Avenue (Box 15, Folder 276)
    - Park Avenue and 19th Street (Box 15, Folder 277)
      includes Parker Building, American Lithographic Co. Building
    - Park Avenue and 22nd Street (Box 15, Folder 278)
      Mills and Gibbs Building
    - Park Avenue and 24th Street (Box 15, Folder 279)
      Ashmond Building
    - Park Avenue and 26th and 27th Streets (Box 15, Folder 280)
      includes Fourth Avenue Building
    - Park Avenue and 28th Street (Box 15, Folder 281)
      Cooper Hewitt Building
    - Park Avenue and 30th Street (Box 15, Folder 282)
      Dodd, Mead & Co. Building
    - Park Avenue and 32nd to 33rd Street (Box 15, Folder 283)
      A.T. Stewart's Hotel for Working Women
    - Park Avenue and 41st to 42nd Street (Box 15, Folder 284)
      Belmont Hotel, Grand Union Hotel
    - 2 Park Avenue (Box 15, Folder 285)
    - 101 Park Avenue (Box 15, Folder 286)
    - 103 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 287)
    - 201 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 288)
      Germania Life Insurance Co. Building
    - 230 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 289)
      New York Central Building
    - 251 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 290)
      Brogan Building
    - 375 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 291)
      Seagram's Building
    - 390 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 292)
      Lever House
    - 445 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 293)
      Universal Pictures Building, Tishman Building
    - 505 Park Avenue (Box 16, Folder 294)
      Aramco Building (Arabian-American Oil Co.)
    - Park Row (Newspaper Row -- Nassau and Spruce Streets) (Box 16, Folder 295)
      includes New York Tribune, World (Pulitzer) and Times, Printing Press Square
    - 15 Park Row (Box 16, Folder 296)
      Park Row Building
    - 21 -- 34 Park Row (Box 16, Folder 297)
      includes stores
    - 38 Park Row (Box 16, Folder 298)
      Potter Building
    - Pearl Street near Hanover Square (Box 16, Folder 299)
      Pearl Street House, Ohio Hotel
    - Btwn. Pearl and Anthony (now Worth) Street (Box 16, Folder 300)
      Mann's Broadway Theatre
    - 122 Pearl Street (Box 16, Folder 301)
      Tappan's Store
    - 142 Pearl Street (Box 16, Folder 302)
      New York Cotton Exchange
    - 234 Pearl Street (Box 16, Folder 303)
      7th Ward Bank
    - 409 -- 415 Pearl Street (Box 16, Folder 304)
      Scott and Bowne Building
    - 541 -- 547 Pearl Street (Box 16, Folder 305)
    - 24 -- 26 Pine Street (Box 16, Folder 306)
      Speyer and Co.
    - 27 -- 33 Pine Street (Box 16, Folder 307)
      includes Kuhn, Hoeb and Co. Building; Kean, Van Cortlandt & Co. Building
    - 34 -- 36 Pine Street (Box 17, Folder 308)
      Union Assurance Society of London Building, Hanover Fire Insurance Co. Building
    - 41 -- 43 Pine Street (Box 17, Folder 309)
      London Liverpool and Globe Insurance Co. Building
    - 93 -- 99 Prince Street (Box 17, Folder 310)
    - 109 -- 111 Prince Street (Box 17, Folder 311)
    - 112 -- 121 Prince Street (Box 17, Folder 312)
    - 133 -- 137 Prince Street (Box 17, Folder 313)
    - Reade Street (Box 17, Folder 314)
    - Rockefeller Center, West 48th -- West 51st Street, between 5th and 6th Avenue (Box 17, Folder 315-316)
      includes Metropolitan Square place
    - South Street (Box 17, Folder 317)
      view from Maiden Lane
    - Spring and Bowery Streets (Box 17, Folder 318)
      Germania Bank Building
    - 114 -- 116 Spring Street (Box 17, Folder 319)
    - 118 Spring Street (Box 17, Folder 320)
    - 121 Spring Street (Box 17, Folder 321)
    - 127 Spring Street (Box 18, Folder 322)
    - 131 -- 137 Spring Street (Box 18, Folder 323)
    - 139 -- 141 Spring Street (Box 18, Folder 324)
    - 1 Times Square (and West 42nd Street) (Box 18, Folder 325)
      Times Building
    - Trinity Place (Box 18, Folder 326)
      Trinity Parish House
    - 46 Trinity Place (Box 18, Folder 327)
    - Union Square (Box 18, Folder 328)
    - Union Square West at 16th Street (Box 18, Folder 329)
      Spingler Building
    - 1 Union Square West (Box 18, Folder 330)
      Lincoln Building
    - 29 Union Square West (Box 18, Folder 331)
      Bank of the Metropolis Building
    - 33 Union Square West (Box 18, Folder 332)
      Union Building (originally Decker Building)
    - United Nations Plaza (Box 18, Folder 333)
    - 13 -- 19 University Place (Box 18, Folder 334)
      Merck Building
    - Varick and Spring Streets (Box 18, Folder 335)
      Varick St. Warehouse
    - Wall Street (Box 18, Folder 336)
      includes Queens Fire Insurance Fire Co. Building, Orient Mutual Building
    - Wall Street views (Box 18, Folder 337)
      Coffee-House Slip, Tontine Coffee House, panic of 1857
    - Wall, Pearl, and Beaver Street (Box 18, Folder 338)
      Eagle Fire Co. Building, Marine Bank Building, Beaver Building
    - Wall Street (Box 18, Folder 339)
      views from William Street (east and west), Trinity Church
    - 8 -- 12 Wall Street (Box 18, Folder 340)
      Astor Building, Mortimer Building
    - 14 -- 47 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 341)
      includes Custom House, Hanover Bank, Merchant's National Bank, Bank of America
    - 48 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 342)
      Bank of New York
    - 49 -- 51 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 343)
      includes Atlantic Mutual Insurance Co., Jones Court
    - 52 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 344)
      National City Bank, New York Life Insurance and Trust Co. Building
    - 55 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 345)
      Merchant's Exchange, U.S. Custom's House
    - 59 -- 63 Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 346)
      Sixty Wall Street, Harriman Building
    - 50 Warren Street (Box 19, Folder 347)
    - 3 -- 5 Washington Place (Box 19, Folder 348)
    - 18 -- 24 Washington Place (Box 19, Folder 349)
    - 100 Washington Square East (Box 19, Folder 350)
    - 258 -- 262 Washington Street, corner of Murray Street (Box 19, Folder 351-352)
      Laing Stores
    - 534 -- 540 Washington Street (Box 19, Folder 353)
      E.R. Durkee & Co. Building
    - 10 Waverly Place (Box 20, Folder 354)
    - 12 Waverly Place (Box 20, Folder 355)
    - 18 Waverly Place (Box 20, Folder 356)
    - 20 -- 22 Waverly Place (Box 20, Folder 357)
    - West and Liberty Street (Box 20, Folder 358)
      Central R.R. of New Jersey Building
    - 90 West Street (Box 20, Folder 359)
      West Street Building
    - 140 West Street (Box 20, Folder 360)
      N.Y. Telephone Building (a.k.a. Barclay-Vesey Building)
    - 463 West Street (Box 20, Folder 361)
      Western Electric Co.
    - West Broadway to Church Street, Worth to Thomas Street (Box 20, Folder 362)
      H.B. Claflin Co. Building
    - West Broadway and Leonard Street (Box 20, Folder 363)
      Lawrence Building
    - 331 -- 335 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 364)
    - 347 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 365)
    - 421 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 366)
    - 425 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 367)
    - 437 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 368)
    - 445 -- 449 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 369)
    - 453 West Broadway (Box 20, Folder 370)
    - 37 -- 61 West Houston Street (Box 20, Folder 371)
    - White Street view (Box 20, Folder 372)
    - 55 White Street (Box 20, Folder 373)
    - William and Beaver Street (Box 20, Folder 374)
      Farmer's Loan and Trust Co.
    - William and Cedar Street (Box 20, Folder 375)
      Kemp Building
    - William Street and Exchange Plaza (Box 20, Folder 376)
      Lord's Court
    - William and Fulton Street (Box 20, Folder 377)
      Royal Building
    - 11 -- 21 William Street (Box 20, Folder 378)
      Corn Exchange Bank Building
    - 95 William Street (Box 20, Folder 379)
      Black Building
    - 163 William Street (Box 21, Folder 380)
      Shell of Australia Building (proposed)
    - 164 William Street (Box 21, Folder 381)
      Germania Fire Insurance Co. Building
    - 214 -- 218 William Street (Box 21, Folder 382)
      Metropolitan Realty Building
    - 232 -- 238 William Street (Box 21, Folder 383)
    - 14 -- 21 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 384)
    - 35 -- 37 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 385)
    - 39 -- 41 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 386)
    - 43 -- 45 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 387)
    - 53 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 388)
    - 55 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 389)
    - 61 -- 63 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 390)
    - 64 -- 68 Wooster Street (Box 21, Folder 391)
    - 69 -- 71 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 392)
    - 80 -- 82 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 393)
    - 97 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 394)
    - 99 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 395)
    - 100 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 396)
    - 105 -- 114 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 397-398)
    - 115 -- 121 Wooster Street (Box 22, Folder 399)
    - 124 -- 126 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 400)
    - 130 -- 132 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 401)
    - 135 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 402)
    - 142 -- 144 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 403)
    - 146 -- 148 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 404)
    - 149 -- 156 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 405)
    - 158 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 406)
    - 236 - 250 Wooster Street (Box 23, Folder 407)
    - World Trade Center models (Box 23, Folder 408)
    - Worth Street and Broadway (Box 23, Folder 409)
    - 65 -- 85 Worth Street (Box 23, Folder 410)
    - Second Avenue and 11th Street (Box 24, Folder 411)
      New York Historical Society Building
    - Third Avenue and 18th Street (Box 24, Folder 412)
      Eimer and Amend Building
    - Fourth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 413)
    - 127 -- 133 Fourth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 414)
      Hancock Building
    - 334 Fourth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 415)
      includes Three Thirty-Four Fourth Avenue Building
    - Fifth Avenue, below 75th Street (Box 24, Folder 416)
      includes view of Madison Square
    - Fifth Avenue and 18th Street (Box 24, Folder 417)
      Chickering Hall
    - Fifth Avenue and 22nd Street (Box 24, Folder 418)
    - Fifth Avenue and 30th Street (Box 24, Folder 419)
      Holland House
    - Fifth Avenue and 32nd Street (Box 24, Folder 420)
      Reed and Barton Building
    - Fifth Avenue and 33rd to 34th Streets (Box 24, Folder 421)
      Knickerbocker Trust Co.Building, Waldorf-Astoria, Hotel Waldorf
    - Fifth Avenue and 44th Street (Box 24, Folder 422)
    - Fifth Avenue and 46th to 47th Street (Box 24, Folder 423)
      Windsor Arcade
    - Fifth Avenue and 57th Street (Box 24, Folder 424)
      Vanderbilt House
    - Fifth Avenue and 65th Street (Box 24, Folder 425)
      residence of Mrs. William Astor
    - Fifth Avenue and 86th Street (Box 24, Folder 426)
      Vanderbilt (Mrs. Cornelius) House
    - 72 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 427)
    - 91 -- 93 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 428)
      St. Denis Hotel
    - 97 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 429)
    - 110 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 430)
      Judge Building
    - 111 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 431)
      Constable Building
    - 139 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 432)
      Corndiac Building
    - 141 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 433)
    - 150 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 434)
      Methodist Book Concern Building
    - 153 -- 157 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 435)
      Scribner Building, Presbyterian Charities Building
    - 160 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 436)
      Mohawk Building
    - 175 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 437)
      Fuller Building (later Flatiron Building)
    - 256 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 438)
    - 284 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 439)
      Wilbraham Building
    - 390 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 440)
      Gorham Manufacturing Co. Building
    - 409 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 441)
      Tiffany and Co. building
    - 510 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 442)
      Manufactures Trust Co. Building
    - 522 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 443)
      Louis Sherry's
    - 527 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 444)
      American Real Estate Co. Building
    - 530 -- 532 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 445)
      Fifth Avenue Bank of New York Building
    - 551 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 446)
      Fred F. French Building
    - 600 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 447)
      Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Co. Building
    - 751 Fifth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 448)
      Van Norden Trust Co. Building
    - Sixth Avenue, between 40th and 42nd Street (Box 24, Folder 449)
      New York Crystal Palace, Bryant Park
    - 161 Sixth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 450)
      Butterick Publishing Co. Building
    - 616 -- 632 Sixth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 451)
      Siegel-Cooper Co. Building, Altman's Building
    - 641 Sixth Avenue (Box 24, Folder 452)
      Simpson-Crawford Co. Dept. Store
    - Seventh Avenue (Box 25, Folder 453)
    - Seventh Avenue and 52nd Street (Box 25, Folder 454)
      Manhattan Storage Warehouse
    - Seventh Avenue and 59th Street (Box 25, Folder 455)
      Central Park Apartments (Navarro Flats)
    - 2081 Seventh Avenue (Box 25, Folder 456)
      Harlem Casino
    - 4th Street and Greene Street (Box 25, Folder 457)
    - 4th Street to Washington Place (Box 25, Folder 458)
      Sachs Building
    - 51 West 10th Street (Box 25, Folder 459)
      R. M. Hunt Studio Building
    - 232 East 11th Street (Box 25, Folder 460)
      St. Mark's-on-the-Bowery (not built)
    - 120 East 12th Street (Box 25, Folder 461)
      Temple Emanu-El
    - 13th Street and Fifth Avenue (Box 25, Folder 462)
    - 13th Street and Ninth Avenue (Box 25, Folder 463)
      Prial Warehouse
    - 13th -- 14th Street, between Avenues B & C (Box 25, Folder 464)
      Architectural Iron Works
    - 12 -- 16 East 14th Street (Box 25, Folder 465)
      Le Boutillier Bros. Building
    - 120 West 14th Street (Box 25, Folder 466)
      Salvation Army Building
    - 9 -- 12 West 15th Street (Box 25, Folder 467)
      New York Hospital
    - 5 -- 7 East 16th Street (Box 25, Folder 468)
      The Geraldine
    - East 17th Street, Union Square (Box 25, Folder 469)
      The Everett Building
    - 18th Street and Broadway (Box 25, Folder 470)
      Aitken and Miller Building
    - 18th Street and Fifth Avenue (Box 25, Folder 471)
    - 9 -- 13 East 18th Street (Box 25, Folder 472)
    - 54 -- 62 West 21st Street (Box 25, Folder 473)